hey everyone thanks for listening to the
grow your life podcast my name is
jeremiah krakowski and if we haven't met
yet i've been helping coaches and
trainers for the last 19 years grow
their businesses scale with offers ads
and sales copy and i want to help you
grow your business whether it be the six
figures seven figures or even eight
figures now today i'm excited because i
have my friend as well as personal
funnel expert who's been helping me and
my clients for the past couple years
i've known him for 15 years he's one of
the best funnel builders that i know at
building designing funnels in the
automation to get the most sales he's
built multiple million dollar funnels
and value ladders and we're gonna work
together today to walk you through how
simple it is for you to use funnels in
your business so they can become clear
how this is going to work so that you
can get
vision for exactly what it's going to be
like to make the kind of money that you
want to make as a coach or trainer so
without further ado help me welcome
steven robbins how you doing steven hey
jeremiah thanks for having me man it's a
pleasure to be here yeah i'm excited
that you said yes to being here so this
is awesome
i'm surprised i said yes to being here i
haven't done this kind of thing in a
long long time that's awesome looks like
you got a funnel right behind you of
some kind right there so yep it's like
all you do is funnels you you got uh how
many how many kids do you have i've got
one kid one puppy and that's a lot
that's right there you go awesome
so
tell me a little bit what got you into
making funnels
it actually that's a really good
question it started with
something non-funnily i got hired to do
something so extremely basic it was
literally making like inspirational
memes for a company like those pictures
you used to see on social media
everywhere okay and it sort of evolved
like little by little by little into hey
we need help building this out we need
help putting this together and i just
kind of had to do
you know it was kind of baptism by fire
i was kind of thrown in there and had to
learn a lot of it as i went but
thankfully i mean i found tons of
amazing coaches and resources out there
to really refine it but i got started
probably the most simple basic way i
could possibly imagine you know now now
i'm building out things that are
really complex in some cases or
not even complex but they just do a lot
of volume um just trying to make sure
that the funnel is there to get the
result that we set out to get so
that's awesome yeah
and i remember when
when we met i actually shared some of my
story i was working for a company uh
danny johnson
um and and i was helping make videos and
then did some marketing with danny and
you were actually working for the same
company you actually knew danny even
from from church way before that
um and then that's how we met and we we
used to hang out and that was way back
when i think i made a lot of the worst
decisions in my life as well so
i'm telling you
it's okay
steven has seen me at my best and my
worst and everywhere in between which is
awesome so that's that's why it's kind
of an honor to even have him on here
which is so cool kind of full circle for
for our journey here
um so this month we actually did this
thing i came up with this random idea i
was like let's audit people's funnels
and stephen went ahead and audited some
people's funnels and came up with this
one of the feedback that we heard was
steven finally gave me the clarity that
i could actually do it
that i could actually
take what's in my head
as a coach as a trainer
and i can see
clearly the path of how i'm going to
reach that level of making seven figures
or making six figures and so that's what
i want to do for all those that are
listening today if you have an idea if
you're a coach if you're a trainer we
want to walk you through some of those
ideas to help you it start to become
real for you
i think that that until you have a
vision for something it's not really
real and i think a lot of people they
they know what they want they see the
end goal but they're like okay what's in
between there how do i get there and so
my goal with this is that together
stephen and i are gonna actually help
fill in those gaps for you and make it
very clear how simple it actually is i
know steven mentioned he's doing some
more complex funnels but the truth is
you don't need to do a complex funnel to
get those kind of results usually what
happens is a lot of people they'll make
a million dollars and then they go
complex to get to that 10 to 20 million
dollar range and that's where it gets
complex but for you to even make a
million or even honestly five million
dollars
it you don't need to be complex and i
think that's where a lot of people miss
it is they think that it has to be so
complex in the beginning when in fact
simple sells
simple is what gets results what have
you noticed steven when building funnels
with people
that are just getting started what's the
number one like
best piece of advice that you would give
somebody who they're a coach they're a
trainer
and
they've heard about funnels they've
heard about marketing
but
they're kind of overwhelmed by all the
stuff what would you say to them yeah
that's a great question you queued it up
really well and i think that probably
the biggest obstacle that people get
tripped up on is like you said the
complexity i mean there's a bajillion
different terms and types of funnels out
there but really the key is just keeping
it simple and straightforward and just
deciding where you want your you know
ideal customer to get to what's their
destination and the simplest path to get
them there and that's really what i mean
that's really all i build out yes there
are some complex funnels but the best
ones the fastest result ones typically
are really surprisingly simple and i
kind of want to
i'm excited we're going to kind of
demystify some of that complexity today
because it's easy to get overwhelmed if
you're not a professional funnel builder
you know but there's really only a few
things you have to put together to
actually get people onto your lists and
actually starting ascending them through
your um your your ladder your value
ladder okay
so i i want to actually unpack what you
just said just a little bit with a few
more questions just to
just to help people understand this we
talk about ascension a value ladder um
but something that you said in the in
the beginning is is that you're
basically moving people
a customer to the desired end goal that
you have
explain what that is because it's like
a coach isn't going to show up at their
house and tie them up and throw them in
the back of their their their truck and
like that's not what we're talking about
moving people to where you want them
right but like
essentially though how does a funnel
help move people's focus in that way
so basically you're taking people who
are online in our case in the digital
world whether they're coming from social
media or an email list that you may have
hopefully you have
various places on the internet
and you're taking them through a series
of pages essentially where your first
step is getting them to take a specific
action usually it's getting their name
on your email list so they're filling
out their information and then hitting a
submit button and then there's a process
that follows that like following up with
them you know what's on the page after
they hit the button or what happens
after they hit the button can you pull
up one of those here real quick actually
yeah let me share my screen i've got my
map my funnel map up here
yeah this is awesome a great example if
people work with you this is actually
something that you're you're offering to
even help people with is is mapping some
of this out and then you actually you
build it for them too right right oh
yeah i've been building symbols for
several years now uh and this is
don't be overwhelmed by this at first if
you're unfamiliar with it but this is
that first page i was talking about so
you're taking people from social media
or wherever they are online we'll put it
that way and then you're directing them
whether it's through advertising or
referrals or your email list or some
kind of retargeting
to this page and this page has something
that will solve a problem for them or
will help them get to their destination
or their goals faster like a shortcut um
there's
there
how do they know that it's going to help
them it that has to do with the copy
and the messaging and and and if you're
listening to this podcast i actually
have a number of episodes that i've done
in the last month that talk about
specifically the copy for your funnels
and and the sales copy and the messaging
and how to dive into that i have a
number of trainings on youtube as well
that kind of dive into that but i
haven't really mapped it out this way so
if you feel lost on something well how
am i going to say that to people go
check out some of those episodes because
i really do a deep dive it's like 20 30
minutes of content just on how do you
say those words right this is more of an
overview for people of kind of how we
move them along there so what you're
doing is essentially you're taking
people from the internet social media or
an ad campaign or a podcast like this
and you're sending them to one page on
your website
correct and that's kind of like a dirty
little secret among funnel builders that
a lot of them won't tell you is the
funnel won't even work unless you know
who your audience is and you have a good
message behind what you're trying to
offer them so like if you're just
putting a bunch of pages together and
hoping somebody will go there nothing's
gonna happen you'll have miserable
results
you'll have people bouncing off the page
you'll have if they buy something
they'll get a refund you don't want to
do that you really want to make sure
take jeremiah's advice get your offer
dialed in get your messaging dialed in
that's kind of like the secret sauce of
a funnel what actually gets people from
point a to point b on you know the brain
the mind level um
directing them leading them telling them
what to do it's all extremely extremely
important
but then these are the mechanisms and
kind of the engine that does that
because yeah if you just have a bunch of
pages with text on them and like
you're telling people to go somewhere
it's almost like a like a really bad
treasure map or like one of those
geo-location geocaching adventures you
know that we used to do
that's not what we want people to do you
want to make it easy for people to go
through the funnel and to get the
information that they're wanting so
explain to them kind of how this works
to do that
so like we said you got your people
coming from somewhere online to the
first page they put in their usually
their email address bare minimum and a
lot of the times their first name
sometimes more
and then once they hit the submit button
or the confirmation button whatever you
have there they're automatically
redirected to the next step in your
funnel which in this case i'm looking at
a three-day challenge or a boot camp
funnel right here or an online event or
something like that that's like three
days five days
you could even do a one day or two day
yeah exactly it it's funny you'll see
the more types of funnels you go through
the similarities are
pretty consistent uh so one thing that
we like to do here this is something
that we highly recommend um is having an
upsell page right out the gate so what
that means is somebody puts in their
information for free and then we give
them the option to get something extra
um with a small amount of money they're
paying to get more um
one thing that's worked super well is
like a vip pass where it's usually like
a q a so they come to the the free event
if it's a live video in a facebook group
or a webinar or a zoom and then if they
bought the extra content they get a
private link that leads them to another
one another room afterward where it's
only the people who bought it and they
get extra content whether it's q a with
whoever speaking
or interviews with experts whatever you
want to deliver there this is a really
good way to offset for instance the ads
cost of your funnel um or if you do it
really well this can even pay for the
the ads cost you can profit on a free
challenge by having an upsell page right
here and all it is is between the opt-in
page where they gave you their
information and the thank you page
because that's the next step is once
they buy or don't buy either way we're
going to tell them thank you on the next
page
and i have it branched off a couple of
different ways here there's a reason
explain the welcome series and the
follow-up
yes okay great thanks for bringing me
back to that so when they put in their
information there's really two things
that happen there's some behind the
scenes that can happen as well but
not only are they getting automatically
redirected to the next funnel step but
they're also getting added to an email
list this is usually done through a crm
or an autoresponder program like you
know mailchimp or aweber or whatever it
is that you're using
and we have a series of emails that we
set to go out automatically to the
people who put their information in
so that we're basically reiterating how
they can get what they came here for
or if they still want to upgrade how to
get the upgrade you know here's another
chance but we're sending them a series
of these emails just to make sure that
they're well taken care of they don't
feel lost or confused or forgotten i
mean the better you are at staying
connected with people in lots of
different ways this is just one of them
the better the results are going to be
at the end of your funnel and through
the next funnels that you do because
you're probably going to have more than
one especially if you're doing a value
ladder like we were talking about before
now let me explain why you're going to
actually do a series of emails and not
just one email that welcomes in um we've
tested this here's one the first thing
we do a series of four emails um we've
done this with tens of thousands of
leads for free events people are never
upset that they got sent for emails to
join a free event they are actually
thankful and grateful all the time so if
you're worried about sending too many
emails in your welcome series um
you're actually gonna have more
complaints if you don't send more emails
uh the second part is if you only send
one email um
the amount of people who actually show
up consume the free content like you'd
think it's so amazing people would
consume it but they don't they get busy
they they they are dealing with gas
prices and inflation and and their child
puked on the floor and all that
themselves and so they are not
remembering about your event as amazing
as it is so you have to keep showing up
to them and doing that and we even
include usually reminding people on the
day of the event that it's coming up an
hour before and even multiple emails
like that
yeah the the human attention span has
only gotten smaller with the
increasing amount of distractions in our
lives and in our world so really keeping
all these touch points really helps keep
them focused and like i said the goal is
to get them to a destination so if you
forget to follow up with them in email
or on the right kind of redirects in
your pages they're not going to ever get
there so just taking care of people i
mean
i kind of view this as a highway and you
want to have lots of road signs that
tell them they're on the right road you
know
or or hey get have you been on the road
and your gps is like you need to turn
around you know you missed your ex
that's a great point these are a great
way to redirect that because all roads
lead to the the final the boot camp the
three days that you want them on there
um or the recordings to it exactly right
yep so we're just keeping people's focus
on getting to the end result for us the
end result is getting them to the end of
this funnel and on to the next funnel uh
so that's why we have that here that's
that's just one set of emails we also
have a set of email follow-up that we do
when they buy if they purchase the
upsell here if you have one we also want
to make sure that those people are taken
care of as well telling them hey thank
you first first and foremost or
congratulations at the very least and
here's the instructions or here's the
information to to get what you paid for
right you know like you don't want your
dollar to get lost you want to actually
get the value out of it uh
so we follow up on as many steps as you
can really uh here and again
like what jeremiah was saying people are
not going to be mad about getting more
than one email i i've been on there's
one email list in particular
where there was a time where i was
getting eight to ten emails in every
single day from this one marketer and i
mean
it was overwhelming to me but i realized
i wasn't their ideal person but they had
extraordinary resort results with their
business they're doing very well you
know so
i mean
people will do more than that this is
really just one a day right here the
welcome the first they're immediately
getting welcome thank you here's your
next step and then the next day is when
they're getting the second email and
then the next day is when they're
getting another email so it's like not
even all at once
um
so i also have another branch off here
you kind of see all these arrows um i
think this is where we had left off at
this step is
i have a page usually for
thank you for people who purchased the
upsell
and also a page for people who said no
to the upsell because there's certain
information that i want to keep from the
people who didn't buy you know i don't
want them to get on the paid thing if
they didn't pay for the thing so i have
a page that just gives them all the
information for the free thing only and
then if they bought it then they get all
of that information plus here's it's
again it's follow-up making sure all the
road signs are going the right way thank
you so much for buying here's how you do
what you came to do what you purchased
and then after that
we have the event itself
and for an event like this the challenge
in boot camp the best results i think
we've both seen still consistently are
like in a facebook group um currently
who knows when that might change things
change a lot online but
usually they're put into a free facebook
group
um which has tons of benefits like the
engagement in other words
people seeing other people doing
comments you know um reactions and
asking questions and posting live video
and stuff kind of there's like there's
something really powerful about not
feeling alone
other people doing what you came to do
you know so that's a great benefit of a
facebook group plus it's easy to manage
it's free and pretty much everybody
already has one and is used to using it
yeah so we poured them all into the
facebook group on the thank you page
usually we have like a few steps you
know step one go to the facebook group
and then there's a button that links to
the facebook group it's really clear
it's never like hey make sure you go to
facebook and type in the search bar to
get to here you know see us hope you get
there you know it's like we try to we
try to plug every hole that we can think
of so anytime you can put a button to
where you want them to go do that
there's a great always right there
billion dollar advice right here you
want to know what creates billion dollar
companies you might be like well i don't
want to create a billion dollar company
so i don't even care about that if you
want to create a million dollar company
if you want to create a six figure
company this is a huge piece of advice
the more steps that you can reduce and
remove
from somebody getting the information
they want the more money you can make
that's right and so like even just
having an extra step where somebody has
to search in a search bar for something
versus you giving them a direct link to
it could actually be a difference in
your sales
yeah
it's true people get lost so easily
that's another point i want to bring up
is when we're sending people through a
funnel i had someone ask not too long
ago they're like hey on the the
marketing page can i also put a link to
my book
and i was like
no
the simple answer is no but the reason
is i have a very specific goal and if we
have anything distracting from that goal
it's going to kill our results so only
this usually in in a lot of cases it's
not even on a website it's on a landing
page where there's no menu there's no
links that take you off of the page the
only way you can get out of it without
going to the next step is if you
manually go manually go and click the x
button what i build here the only way to
move forward is putting your information
in and hitting the button and then you
go to the next step like it's i mean
imagine again a highway like there's
walls on the sides usually you know it's
not like a regular roadway right here
turn left here it's we want to get you
to this step next and so there's nothing
to distract you from that same with here
when you're going to say hey join the
facebook group i don't want to distract
you with hey go search for us on
facebook hope you make it no it's go
follow us go right here go
go leave us a review go read this book
yeah people need to be led i mean a lot
of times people need to be told what to
do especially if things are confusing i
mean if you have if your clientele is
older especially i mean
doing all the work for them as much as
you can in this manner is really
important and here's another great piece
of advice is pretend like you're leading
a group of of uh
five and ten-year-olds
yeah
um
like simplify it that much
because
okay and and i and this is not to be
offensive to anybody that people are
stupid
right it's just that when you're
bringing somebody into an environment
like this most people don't go through
this type of an environment and so the
more that they can feel taken care of
the more likely they are to actually buy
from you
yes that's exactly right and that's that
plays in every step just like we're
saying here no distractions on this page
in the email we're constantly
redirecting them to the next page or
inviting them to step back in at this
step if they didn't yep we're always
trying to get them to go down this
highway where we want them to go
um and then you know once we get them
into the facebook group or wherever the
live event is happening we've got a
little bit of a formula that we follow
for the three days yeah so usually it's
like day one you're unpacking the vision
of what the promised result is that you
gave them
you then kind of give the promised
results on day two you kind of give like
the meat and potatoes that they like
sort of signed up for that way you can
deliver it and now here's the thing
are you gonna have people complain on
day one that you didn't actually give
the promised result yes you are
and that's okay and they will never show
up today too
but what the truth is is they actually
prove that they actually weren't your
qualified customer at that point and
that's what i love is actually by doing
this model as day one sort of weeds
people out
by not just giving it to them at first
you're you're you're sort of training
them to be patient just a little bit and
working on
framing you need to frame
what it is that you're going to teach
them
i heard a phrase that
the best way to sell online is to create
the environment for it and by working on
the vision that people have you're
creating that environment for them to
buy you're creating that environment for
them to be most likely to receive the
information
okay so that's what day one is all about
is kind of setting the stage for day two
to give information and then day three
you sell them something and i will say
this do not ever do this model of a
three day event without having something
to sell at the end
that is probably one of the most unwise
things and the biggest way to flush
money down the toilet
is to not have something to sell at the
end okay
and so and and so then with that then
they go into the offer series and then
the offer series is is a series of
usually emails twice a day
written from different perspectives
answering
the different objections that the person
will have
and what we'll usually do is actually
pull those from if we have an upsell
that has a q a in it
we'll actually pull the objections from
that upsell and handle them
in the offer series we'll pull them from
the comments the questions that people
asked we'll answer those questions that
people had about our offer so oftentimes
we'll we'll have for many of our clients
that stephen and i have worked with
work through a three-day challenge like
this and we'll do the same challenge six
or seven times and pay attention to what
are the most common questions that are
asked and then we'll literally put those
into our offer series we'll literally
put those into our content that way
we're leading people with exactly what
they're thinking almost like we're
reading their mind people will be like
how did you know i was thinking that
well because
3 000 people before you were 300 before
you sat the exact same question and
that's how you really dial in your
messaging here's what's cool is
as once you do this by the way then
you're going to want to go back and
probably change the messaging of your
actual initial landing page we're doing
that with a client right now we ran the
same challenge six times realized hmm it
was almost good enough but we need to
change the angle just a little bit and
and by doing that you're able to hone in
more and more the more niche you get
that's where your money comes in and
your profits come in
now this model of the three day
challenge or bootcamp um the other thing
that you'll want to try out again if you
don't have a big email list you don't
have a lot of followers doing it for
free is a great way to test it out get
your feet wet um but the way to make the
most amount of money is actually running
a three-day challenge boot camp where
you charge for it
and and you run it as an event where
they have to pay you 47 or 97 to join
for three to five days those people that
are willing to pay are way more
qualified than who show up for a free
training okay so stephen here's a
question that i have for you is if
somebody's just getting started doing
this again we tried to make it as simple
as possible can you simplify this even
more for people
to talk about
like i would say if they even just focus
on that opt-in page
and the thank you page and maybe the
welcome series as three things they
don't even necessarily need to do the
upsell right away though it's
recommended
they might not even need to do a
three-day boot camp this same model
works if they just want to do a one day
like a webinar let me touch on one thing
real fast before we leave this one right
here super important just as important
as having the welcome emails is reminder
emails if you have a live event or a
pre-scheduled event in some way we
usually do
bare minimum
one day before the event happens we're
telling them hey the event is starting
here's how you get there here's how you
access it here's how you participate and
then also one hour before now you can
also do more like the morning of or two
days before depending on how far away
the event is and
how thorough you want to be on your
follow-up but these are just as
important as the any other piece of
follow-up in this entire series is
reminding them because again people
forget people have things that go on in
their life emergencies circumstances or
just
forgetfulness so having that in there
the same way as these you can schedule
them out um is super important
awesome
explain like in the simplest language
how somebody could use this and get
started and maybe put something out
there in the next week or so yeah so i
mean the basis of this funnel is like
this the foundation of it is
having a way to collect
people's information as they get to your
page
and then getting them the message like
telling them how they're going to
consume what they came here for so you
really the
the smallest simplest version of this
funnel is opt-in page thank you page
and and then from there however you're
going to deliver the content whether
it's a download button or a social group
or zoom whatever you're
following the same rules you're just
keeping it really simple directing them
from point a
to point b or a to z and you're
following up with email and any other
ways that you do have set to follow up
with people i mean if a lot of these
funnels are built on the same process
it's either opt-in thank you or check
out thank you that's kind of like the
basis of every single funnel that i know
of for the most part you know uh does
that does that seem like it simplifies
it a little bit it it does and scroll
down to some of the other funnels that
you have here on this page here i know
you had a couple yeah
so then here's the next funnel that we
have here we this is like an e-book
funnel looks kind of similar again
opt-in page uh upsell thank you page
offer series the difference is instead
of them joining an event your ebook sort
of takes place at that event yeah it's
like an instant gratification where the
second they get to the confirmation page
they can download it there's a there's
another approach i've seen where you can
delay that while you're telling them
you know what they can buy here as well
this is one way to do this where they're
opting in they have an option to take an
upsell which can just be again maybe
you're elaborating on the ebook or maybe
you're adding to the topic
there's a lot of different angles that
you can take in here just make sure that
it's valuable and it helps them solve
the problems and it matches with the
audience and the offer i mean like you
want things to be consistent throughout
yes otherwise you're going to lose
people
and let's talk about that real quick so
let's say that you have an ebook that's
about how to get more clients in your
marketing but then you have an upsell on
how to um
how to
build the right graphics on your website
that's a little
we'd think that they'd be the same
customer but those are completely
disconnected offers right um and so and
i see a lot of people make that mistake
in the beginning because that's the only
content they have sometimes you need to
create a new piece of content for your
upsell that matches and complements
whatever your main opt-in is so for
instance if you have a book on the topic
of marketing say hey i did a five-part
training series right here for
about and then you literally reiterate
the same topic as the free ebook
and then that becomes the upsell another
another um example of an upsell is like
if your offer created a new problem for
them let's solve that in the upsell for
example
if the offer is how to get more people
on your email on your marketing list
maybe the new problem that they have is
they don't even have a marketing list
you know so it's like here's how you
know you can have something in here that
solves that problem for them or you know
here's here's the simple process for
getting an autoresponder plugged into
your funnels and using it to communicate
with your list seven bucks or whatever
your offer is there so you're basically
solving a problem that you created for
them is a
another option you have for your upsell
that's awesome and
following up with email and then
redirecting them to the thank you page
so that they can consume what they came
for super important
and then you make an offer series with
them in that but you also want to make
your offer in the ebook and in the
upsell at that point because there's not
an event that they're going to so you
don't you don't ever want any point of
your funnel to where it just stops and
again this is another amateur thing that
i see a lot of people do is they they
give they deliver content and then
there's no call to action and i've even
heard people say well i don't want to
seem like i'm
needy i don't want to seem like i'm like
needing them to buy
my friends they they're not going to see
it that way
and and i actually used to be somebody
that thought that i'm like i'm going to
deliver them so much value with no ask
and they're just going to buy from me
because of that unfortunately that was a
very that is a very wrong way of
thinking
you need to have some kind of a call to
action at the end of every single thing
that you deliver to people including a
free ebook including your blog posts
your podcasts your your emails different
things like that
yeah that's a great that's that's so
true and another way that i've seen that
implemented that i like
is what's commonly referred to as an
offer wall so like on your thank you
page let's say we're looking at the free
ebook here's the download button for it
here's how you get it below it can
simply be their next steps on the page
itself plus you've got it in the emails
you know plus you're telling about it if
you have a welcome video hey your next
step is you know whatever your verbage
is there but these are usually your next
step or by the way you might also like
because the bottom line is
whoever came through here came to you
for solutions for your help for your
your
um ability to see what they can't see
and you're telling them here's some more
stuff that's going to help you things
that you might not even know that you
don't even know yet you know so it's not
even like feeling like i'm needy or
something it's this is a way to serve
people is telling them how to get to the
next level you know how to take that
next step whether it's with you or
whatever they're doing um but it's i
like to think of it as a way to serve
people telling you know you're not
leaving them hanging here either just
like you're not leaving them hanging
when they first stopped in and you're
reminding them or you're telling them
you know repeatedly how to get with the
game you don't want to leave them
hanging on the last page of your funnel
either so tell them where to go next
it's kind of the bottom line you know
you got to from point a to point b but
guess what there's a point c too here
you guys got to get there you know so
just kind of implementing various ways
to get them to the next step
hey steven do you think you could um
export this scroll down real quick and
show them all the different funnels
let's we're not going to talk about all
of them right now because we just don't
have enough time here but keep scrolling
down
so we have the mini class funnel right
there again opt-in page upsell mini
class kind of takes the place of the
challenge or the ebook but you follow
the same process mindset practical
application keep scrolling down some
more uh all the rules offer all the
rules apply pretty much to every single
funnel type sure you're following up
making sure the distractions are gone
and you're simplifying it and directing
people where to go keep scrolling down
just
all of them show them the different ones
you have here keep going
high ticket okay so here's here's the
thing steven do you think you'd be able
to export this and we can give this as a
pdf to everybody
that's listening to this podcast so
that'll be on my website on the episode
of this podcast there'll be a link to a
google drive link to download the pdf
of this for you to reference yourself
later now here's the the last thing i
want to talk about is the high ticket
funnel
and this is
that looks a little different than the
rest of the funnels
yeah explain what's going on here
so
generally a rule of thumb
that i like to go by is the more you're
asking from somebody the more personal
you want to be with them the more like
time you want to spend with them not
necessarily
not necessarily saying you've got to
jump on a six-hour call with somebody
but we're just saying for for something
like this high ticket is usually in the
thousands if not tens of thousands of
dollars and sometimes more so making it
really personal um high touch is a term
that i've used for this kind of thing
getting them on a phone call or even
better now everybody knows how to use a
zoom after the last couple of years and
you've got to you have the ability to
see somebody face to face so what we're
doing is we're having them apply here
for the high ticket in this case there
can be an opt-in here instead that's
just name and email but an application
really kind of helps frame somebody up
for
selling themselves on why
you know they're trying to tell you i
want to be in your program and here's
why you know i want to work with you
further and here's why um plus it puts a
little bit more time for them like
they're spending more time giving you
the information to handle all of their
problems offer them solutions the
application can give you so much
information usually on here it can be
you know what do you struggle with most
in your business what is your goal in
your business like these are usually
questions that like a traditional sales
person has to end um sorry handle with
somebody anyway but we're really getting
to know them in an application and then
that goes to usually a booking page i
didn't have it on here i could put it on
here but um something like calendly is a
really good tool where you can integrate
it with it go to the website calendly
this is actually going to be a hugely
valuable to your funnels if you're
wanting to like book calls with people
um and and i think they have a free
level that works for most people don't
they
uh yes they do they do uh there's free
and paid you can get different
integrations with the paid but the free
works really well yeah you can do pretty
much everything you need to do with the
free one and then you basically sync it
up to either your google calendar your
you know your apple calendar
and tell it you know these are the times
i would accept an appointment and then
somebody can go in and choose what time
works well for them so it's it's really
handy you can kind of see all the
features and how it works on this page
here but
calendly is probably my my recommended
tool for that and we're going to put a
link to your calendly on the this as
well where they can actually if they
want to
um have you build their funnel or do a
consult with them about their funnel
they can schedule a time with you
by the way think of it this way this
podcast episode is a little bit of a
mini funnel for what stephen and i do
it's kind of a more of a high ticket
funnel right to work with steven's gonna
cost you a couple thousand dollars
you know to build out the whole thing
working with me my coaching starts at
fourteen thousand dollars and so
if you want to do a consult or a
discovery call with me about coaching
with you where i help you work on your
messaging your strategy your marketing
and build all that out you can schedule
that on my website at jeremiahkowski.com
by clicking on the link that says
one-on-one coaching can you pull that up
real quick the link over at my website
and we're actually going to show them
what that looks like here real quick
um so like if you go over to my website
right here okay you're on this podcast
episode you're kind of in my funnel if
you listen to my podcast i sort of treat
my podcast like a mini class funnel okay
and at the end of it here's my call to
action i'm giving it to you so you click
on 101 coaching scroll to the bottom of
the page all the way down
see some testimonies
right there but at the very bottom of
the page it says schedule discovery call
can you click that link steven yeah and
so right here you can schedule a free
45-minute discovery call with me this is
my calendly link where new clients can
schedule a time with me and we can go
over if they are serious about
one-on-one coaching with me about doing
that so you can go over to my website
schedule that call with me to talk about
building your business together if you
just want the funnels done you can
schedule that call with steven with the
link that's at the bottom of this
stephen thank you so much for your time
here to show people all of this truly
like i think anybody can do this no
matter what their business is no matter
what their niche is do you have any
final words of of wisdom for people if
maybe again they're still feeling kind
of overwhelmed by all of this what's the
first thing that they could focus on and
and really what what are the potential
results that they could get by building
a funnel like this
that's a bigger question than it sounds
at first the first rule i would say is
keep it simple
second rule is make sure you've got your
your you know your ideal customer or
your avatar set up lined up um and your
offer and your messaging match that
person i mean it's it's so crucial like
i said it's like the dirty little secret
that most funnel builders don't want you
to know because that's kind of like the
fuel for the whole thing you know
uh and then getting started just taking
action whether you have a landing page
builder or a funnel builder yourself
just getting in there and starting
somewhere make it really simple if you
have to go thank you for a opt-in page
and a thank you page is you know the
first step for you and if you don't know
how to do that if you don't have the
time or you don't have the focus because
you're busy building your your content
uh reach out for help somebody like me
would be happy to help um i'd be happy
to take your call and see you know what
we can do
awesome
thanks steven this has been great i
think this is really going to help
people as well
um feel free to reach out if you guys
have any questions about your funnel
your messaging things like that um you
know we'd be happy to help point you in
the right direction i have so much
training on my youtube on my podcast
about finding your your customer avatar
about your messaging that's that's kind
of where i dive into most of my business
is kind of really diving into that and
really honing in your messaging by the
way
just a case study for messaging
we tweaked the messaging for a client
and it got a 500 increase in the results
that they got from a losing campaign
that was losing money to being
profitable just by tweaking one word in
the copy that changed the messaging and
so that's how important the avatar is is
that's what really
is like the difference maker between
okay is this a profitable funnel or is
this not
it's getting the messaging down but i
think having a funnel is so important
even if you don't have your messaging
perfect having a funnel is extremely
valuable and steven's here to help you
with building some of that as well yeah
thanks for having me man i appreciate it
it's a lot of fun
all right
grow your life everybody if this episode
has helped you be sure to share it with
somebody if you got somebody that you
know that's building funnel share this
episode with them make sure you go
through the other episodes as well to
grow your life podcast there's so much
content for you for free that i give
away on my youtube and the grow your
life podcast it's gonna help you if
you're a coach if you're a trainer to
get the results that you want we'll talk
soon everybody have a good one